<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Act1 - HHC 2024</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/act1/index.html</link>
    <description>With Santa away, Wombley Cube and Alabaster Snowball have each tried to lead. Surely they won’t mess up the naughty and nice list…&#xA;Help Bow, Morcel, and Jewell solve their challenges.&#xA;This division among the elves can’t be good. Surely it won’t get any worse.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 14:19:45 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/act1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Curling</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act1/curling/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 14:18:57 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act1/curling/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Team up with Bow Ninecandle to send web requests from the command line using Curl, learning how to interact directly with web servers and retrieve information like a pro!&#xA;Solution Easy mode Assignment 1 Unlike the defined standards of a curling sheet, embedded devices often have web servers on non-standard ports. Use curl to retrieve the web page on host “curlingfun” port 8080. If you need help, run the ‘hint’ command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frosty Keypad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act1/frosty-keypad/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 14:19:14 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act1/frosty-keypad/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective In a swirl of shredded paper, lies the key. Can you unlock the shredder’s code and uncover Santa’s lost secrets?&#xA;Hints UV light Numbers found from lighting at the keypad using the UV light:&#xA;[ 2, 6, 7, 8 ] Hint from the book This is the hint we get:&#xA;Thinking about it, it appears to correpond to&#xA;page:word:letter Using this formula I got:&#xA;Sequence From book 2:6:1 S 4:19:3 A 6:1:1 N 3:10:4 T 14:8:3 A Somehow I got “SANTA”.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware Hacking 101</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act1/hardware-hacking/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 14:19:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act1/hardware-hacking/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective (main) Ready your tools and sharpen your wits—only the cleverest can untangle the wires and unlock Santa’s hidden secrets!&#xA;Hardware Hacking 101 Part 1 Objective Jingle all the wires and connect to Santa’s Little Helper to reveal the merry secrets locked in his chest!&#xA;Silver In the hint section I found this helpful hint:&#xA;On the Cutting Edge From: Morcel Nougat Terminal: Hardware Part 1 Hey, I just caught wind of this neat way to piece back shredded paper!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>