<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Act2 - HHC 2024</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/index.html</link>
    <description>This is a new chapter.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:18:55 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/act2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/mobile-analysis/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:18:24 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/mobile-analysis/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Help find who has been left out of the naughty AND nice list this Christmas. Please speak with Eve Snowshoes for more information.&#xA;Hints Mobile Analysis Easy - Tools&#xA;From Objective Description Eve Snowshoes Mobile Analysis Try using apktool or jadx Mobile Analysis Easy - Missing&#xA;From Objective Description Eve Snowshoes Mobile Analysis Maybe look for what names are included and work back from that? Mobile Analysis Hard - Format</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Path</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/drone-path/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:18:31 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/drone-path/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Help the elf defecting from Team Wombley get invaluable, top secret intel to Team Alabaster. Find Chimney Scissorsticks, who is hiding inside the DMZ.&#xA;Solution Silver From the hamburger menu I accesses “FileShare” and got this landing page, where I could download a fritjolf-Path.kml file:&#xA;Opening this .kml file in Google Earth, it opens up and shows a phrase:&#xA;GUMDROP1 By looking at these two things I have just discovered, there is something strange going on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powershell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/powershell/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:18:37 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/powershell/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objecetive Team Wombley is developing snow weapons in preparation for conflict, but they’ve been locked out by their own defenses. Help Piney with regaining access to the weapon operations terminal.&#xA;Solution Silver Task 1 There is a file in the current directory called ‘welcome.txt’. Read the contents of this file Get-Content -Path &#34;.\welcome.txt&#34; Output&#xA;System Overview The Elf Weaponry Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) system safeguards access to a classified armory containing elf weapons.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowball Showdown</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/snowball-showdown/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:18:46 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/snowball-showdown/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Wombley has recruited many elves to his side for the great snowball fight we are about to wage. Please help us defeat him by hitting him with more snowballs than he does to us.&#xA;Solution Bronze Once loading the game, we get presented with a loading screen detailing how to play the game:&#xA;And this is the general game area:&#xA;By inspecting the GET parameter in URL, I found this:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Kc7</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/act2/microsoft-kc7/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 13:18:55 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/act2/microsoft-kc7/index.html</guid>
      <description>Welcome to your mission to solve the The Great Elf Conflict! To do so, you’ll need to harness the power of KQL (Kusto Query Language) to navigate through the data and uncover crucial evidence.&#xA;Your next step is to meet with Eve Snowshoes, Cyber Engineer, at the at the North Pole Cyber Defense Unit. Eve is known for unmatched expertise in KQL and has been eagerly awaiting your arrival. Alt text</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>