<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prologue - HHC 2024</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/prologue/index.html</link>
    <description>Welcome back to the Geese Islands! Let’s help the elves pack up to return to the North Pole.&#xA;Talk to Jingle, Angel, and Poinsettia about their challenges.&#xA;This is a new chapter at the Frosty Beach&#xA;Jingle Ringford (Frosty’s Beach)&#xA;Welcome to the Geese Islands and the 2023 SANS Holiday Hack Challenge!&#xA;I’m Jingle Ringford, one of Santa’s many elves.&#xA;…&#xA;Just kidding! It’s actually the 2024 SANS Holiday Hack Challenge!</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 12:19:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Orientation Challenge</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prologue/orientation-challenge/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 09:59:39 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prologue/orientation-challenge/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Talk to Jingle Ringford on Christmas Island and get your bearings at Geese Islands&#xA;Question The question and what to do is pretty self explanatory.&#xA;Answer As I said …</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf Connect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prologue/elf-connect/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 10:51:56 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prologue/elf-connect/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Help Angel Candysalt connect the dots in a game of connections.&#xA;Hints From Hint Angel Candysalt WOW! A high score of 50,000 points! That’s way beyond the limit! With only four rounds and a max of 400 points per round, the top possible score should be 1,600 points. So, how did someone get to 50,000? Something unusual must be happening! If you’re curious, you might want to check under the hood.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elf Minder 9000</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/prologue/elf-minder-9000/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 12:19:21 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/prologue/elf-minder-9000/index.html</guid>
      <description>Objective Assist Poinsettia McMittens with playing a game of Elf Minder 9000.&#xA;Hints From Hint Poinsettia McMittens Be sure you read the “Help” section thoroughly! In doing so, you will learn how to use the tools necessary to safely guide your elf and collect all the crates. Poinsettia McMittens Some levels will require you to click and rotate paths in order for your elf to collect all the crates. Poinsettia McMittens When developing a video game—even a simple one—it’s surprisingly easy to overlook an edge case in the game logic, which can lead to unexpected behavior.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>